Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Area
  - 693 Broadway, circa 1965 - 1975 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Coffee Shop, 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - 693 Broadway (Detail), wsa_1_2_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 8)
  - Basketball Court - West 4th Street, 1981 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Basketball Game, undated; wsa_1_3_01; DuBois, Gaston; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_02; Pena, John; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_03; Pena, John; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_04; Pena, John; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_05; Pena, John; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Bleecker Street, 1955-1983 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Bleecker Street Cinema, Bleecker Between West Broadway and Thompson, wsa_1_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Greenwich Hotel, Bleecker Looking West Toward Sullivan, undated; wsa_1_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Yipster Front, 1981; wsa_1_4_03; Slavkovsky, R.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Bleecker Street Between MacDougal and Sullivan, undated; wsa_1_4_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Bleecker Street Cinema Marquee, undated; wsa_1_4_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Bleecker Street Between West Broadway and Thompson, undated; wsa_1_4_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Building, East End of Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_1_4_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - Bleecker Street Between MacDougal and Sullivan, undated; wsa_1_4_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - Bleecker Street at Sullivan Street, undated; wsa_1_4_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Bleecker Street at Thompson Street, undated; wsa_1_4_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Phone Booths, Bleecker Street, 1983; wsa_1_4_11; Chait, Marc W.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - Saint Barnabas House, 1983; wsa_1_4_12; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 12)
    - Corner of Bleecker and Mulberry Streets, 1983; wsa_1_4_13; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 13)
    - Bleecker Bob's Records, 1983; wsa_1_4_14; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 14)
    - Cafe Rafio, undated; wsa_1_4_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 15)
    - Bleecker Street Between Thompson and West Broadway, undated; wsa_1_4_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 16)
    - 175 Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_1_4_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 17)
    - Men on Bleecker Street, Looking East Toward Thompson, undated; wsa_1_4_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 18)
    - Ganga's Used Clothing Store, Undated; wsa_1_4_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 19)
    - Folk City, undated; wsa_1_4_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 20)
    - Deli-Box Restaurant, Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_1_4_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 21)
    - Bleecker Street Between Greene and Mercer, 1955; wsa_1_4_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 22)
    - Looking North Up Thompson Street, undated; wsa_1_4_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 23)
    - Bleecker and Sullivan Streets, undated; wsa_1_4_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 24)
    - New York Switchboard Peoples Information Center, undated; wsa_1_4_25; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 25)
    - New York Switchboard Peoples Information Center, undated; wsa_1_4_26; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 26)
    - New York Switchboard Peoples Information Center, undated; wsa_1_4_27; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 27)
    - Ambulance, Mercer and Bleecker Streets, undated; wsa_1_4_28; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 28)
    - Saint Baranabas House, Interior, 1983; wsa_1_4_29; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 29)
  - Broadway, circa 1964-1990 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - 640 Broadway at West 4th Street, wsa_1_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - 640 Broadway at West 4th Street, undated; wsa_1_5_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Costume Shop Window, undated; wsa_1_5_03; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Billy Idol Fans Waiting in Line for Tickets, circa 1980 - 1990; wsa_1_5_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Child with Pumpkin Toy, wsa_1_5_05; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - 707 Broadway, 1964; wsa_1_5_06; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Crowd Outside of Tower Records, 1984; wsa_1_5_07; Chen, Andy; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Tower Records, 1983; wsa_1_5_08; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 8)
    - 657 Broadway, 1981; wsa_1_5_09; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 9)
    - 561 Broadway, 1979; wsa_1_5_10; Smith, Jeff; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 10)
    - 561 Broadway, 1979; wsa_1_5_11; Smith, Jeff; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 11)
    - Building with Scaffolding, undated; wsa_1_5_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 12)
    - Church, undated; wsa_1_5_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 13)
    - People Waiting in Line Outside of Tower Records, undated; wsa_1_5_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 14)
    - 561 Broadway, undated; wsa_1_5_15; Smith, Jeff; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 15)
    - People Waiting in Line Outside of Tower Records, undated; wsa_1_5_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 16)
  - Church of the Strangers, Mercer Street (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Church of the Stranger, Mercer Street (engraving), wsa_1_6_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Clinton Court (drawing), 1854 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Clinton Court - Drawn Map of Area Between 6th Avenue, 8th Street, Waverly Place and MacDougal Street, 1854; wsa_1_7_01; Perris, William; Paper Reproduction of Drawn Map Taped onto 8 x 10 Paper (Box 175, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - General views -Contact Sheets, Miscellaneous, cuid17561 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets
  - Diners, Cafes, Restaurants (1 of 2) (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - "Rocks in Your Head" Record Shop, 1981; wsa_2_1_01; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - "Rocks in Your Head" Record Shop, 1981; wsa_2_1_02; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - "Rocks in Your Head" Record Shop (interior), 1981; wsa_2_1_03; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Waitress, Cafe Rosa Diner, undated; wsa_2_1_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Tio Pepe Cafe (exterior), undated; wsa_2_1_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Cook, New Dehli Restaurant, 1983; wsa_2_1_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Arch Cafe, Washington Square South and Thompson Streets, 1905; wsa_2_1_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Cafe Figaro, undated; wsa_2_1_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Barista, undated; wsa_2_1_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Restaurant Interior, undated; wsa_2_1_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Cafe Borgia, undated; wsa_2_1_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Campus Coffee Shop, undated; wsa_2_1_12 (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Cafe, undated; wsa_2_1_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Buffalo Roadhouse, 1975; wsa_2_1_14 (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Villa Marbona Italian Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Campus Coffee Shop and Environs, From Above, 1965; wsa_2_1_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Menu, The Captain's Table, undated; wsa_2_1_17 (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Cook in Cafeteria, undated; wsa_2_1_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Cook, Loeb Commons Cafeteria, 1980; wsa_2_1_19; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Cook, Cafeteria, undated; wsa_2_1_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Dirty Floor, Loeb Cafeteria, undated; wsa_2_1_21; Morris, R.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Trinity Place, undated; wsa_2_1_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Restaurant (interior), undated; wsa_2_1_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Pantry, Loeb Cafeteria, undated; wsa_2_1_24; Morris, R.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 24)
    - Store Interior, undated; wsa_2_1_25; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 25)
    - The Captain's Table, undated; wsa_2_1_26; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 26)
    - Produce Market, undated; wsa_2_1_27; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 27)
    - "The Loading Zone", 1981; wsa_2_1_28; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 28)
    - Caffe Pane e Cioccolato, 1981; wsa_2_1_29; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 29)
    - Granados Cafe, undated; wsa_2_1_30; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 30)
    - Star of Siam Restaurant (interior), 1983; wsa_2_1_31; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 31)
    - Wok Restaurant, 1980; wsa_2_1_32; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 32)
    - Hopper's Restaurant and Market, 1976; wsa_2_1_33; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 33)
    - Star of Siam Restaurant (interior), 1983; wsa_2_1_34; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 34)
    - Rocks in Your Head Record Shop (interior), 1981; wsa_2_1_35; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 35)
    - Record, 1981; wsa_2_1_36; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 36)
    - The Cookery, undated; wsa_2_1_37; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 37)
    - Luncheonette, undated; wsa_2_1_38; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 38)
    - Espresso Machine, undated; wsa_2_1_39; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 39)
    - Man, undated; wsa_2_1_40; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 40)
    - Man, Rock and Roll Pizza, undated; wsa_2_1_41; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 41)
    - La Groceria Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_42; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 42)
    - La Groceria Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_43; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 43)
    - Lone Star Cafe, 13th Street and 5th Avenue, undated; wsa_2_1_44; Smith, Jeff; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 44)
    - Star of Siam Restaurant (interior), undated; wsa_2_1_45; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 45)
    - Star of Siam Restaurant (interior), 1983; wsa_2_1_46; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 46)
    - Steve's Ice Cream Shop, 1983; wsa_2_1_47; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 47)
    - Dual Pallete Restaurant (interior), undated; wsa_2_1_48; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 48)
    - Waitress, Cafe Rosa, undated; wsa_2_1_49; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 49)
    - Waiter, Dual Pallete Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_50; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 50)
    - The Pitaria, 1984; wsa_2_1_51; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 51)
    - Xenia II Greek Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_52; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 52)
    - Baked Goods at the Pitaria, 1984; wsa_2_1_53; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 53)
    - Quantum Leap Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_54; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 54)
    - Quantum Leap Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_55; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 55)
    - The Pitaria, 1984; wsa_2_1_56; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 56)
    - Tio Pepe Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_57; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 57)
    - Pizzeria Uno Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_58; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 58)
    - Campus Coffee Shop, undated; wsa_2_1_59; Rhyins, Will; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 59)
    - Delion Grocery, 1980; wsa_2_1_60; Nguyen, Andy; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 60)
    - Bleecker Gourmet Delicatessen, 1984; wsa_2_1_61; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 61)
    - Thomson Gourmet Deli-Grocery, 1984; wsa_2_1_62; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 62)
    - Caffe Pane e Cioccolato, 1981; wsa_2_1_63; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 63)
    - Restaurant Interior, undated; wsa_2_1_64; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 64)
    - Bitable Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_65; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 65)
    - Restaurant and Wine Cellar, undated; wsa_2_1_66; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 66)
    - Sidewalk Sign: The Pitaria, 1984; wsa_2_1_67; Patel, Samir; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 67)
  - Diners, Cafes, Restaurants (2 of 2) (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Red Witch Bar, undated; wsa_2_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Noonday Cafe, Trinity Church, undated; wsa_2_2_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Bigelow's Diner, undated; wsa_2_2_03; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Many Tossing Pizza Dough Outside of Rock And Roll Pizza, circa 1980 - 1989; wsa_2_2_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Hot Dog Cart, undated; wsa_2_2_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Village Gate, undated; wsa_2_2_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - Mercer Street, 1965; wsa_2_2_07; Seligson, Stanley; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - Harout's Restaurant and Acme Textile Co., 1964; wsa_2_2_08; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - Cafe Figaro, undated; wsa_2_2_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 9)
    - 116 MacDougal Street, undated; wsa_2_2_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 10)
    - Village Sugar Bowl Luncheonette, and Environs, wsa_2_2_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 11)
    - Sweet Basil Restaurant (interior), 1975; wsa_2_2_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 12)
    - Sandolino Restaurant, 1975; wsa_2_2_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - McBell's Kitchen, 1975; wsa_2_2_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 14)
    - Hungry Charley's, undated; wsa_2_2_15; Magnuson, Erik; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 15)
    - Caffe da Alfredo, 1975; wsa_2_2_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 16)
    - Mills Tavern Bar and Grill, undated; wsa_2_2_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 17)
    - Steve's Ice Cream, 1983; wsa_2_2_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 18)
    - Building, 1965; wsa_2_2_19; Seligson, Stanley; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 19)
    - Aquarius Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_2_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 20)
    - "Harout's: A Place to Rap or to Stand Alone and Think", 1969; wsa_2_2_21; Zabriskie, Peter; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 21)
    - Aquarius Restaurant (interior), 1970; wsa_2_2_22; Sherwin, Gene; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 22)
    - Tio Pepe Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_2_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 23)
    - Tempting Food and Drink (restaurant), undated; wsa_2_2_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 24)
    - Wine Shop (interior), undated; wsa_2_2_25; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 25)
    - People Talking on Sidewalk, 1984; wsa_2_2_26; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 26)
    - The Captain's Table Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_2_27; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 27)
    - Clam Bar at O. Henry's, undated; wsa_2_2_28; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 2, Item 28)
  - East 8th Street (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - E.S. Wilentz's 8th Street Bookshop, undated; wsa_2_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Nathan's, Eighth Street and Sixth Avenue, undated; wsa_2_3_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Everything Natural Health Food Store and Pop's Candy Store, undated; wsa_2_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Eighth Street, undated; wsa_2_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Eighth Street, undated; wsa_2_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Wilentz's Books, undated; wsa_2_3_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - 69 Cent Shops, undated; wsa_2_3_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Wilentz's Books (exterior), undated; wsa_2_3_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 2 x 5 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - Metropolitan Savings Bank, undated; wsa_2_3_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - 69 Cent Shops, undated; wsa_2_3_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 10)
    - Street Signs: Avenue of the Americas and West 8th Street, undated; wsa_2_3_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 11)
    - Polka-dot Shoes in Store Window, undated; wsa_2_3_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 12)
    - Street Signs: 5th Avenue and West 8th Street, undated; wsa_2_3_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 13)
    - Record Factory (store), undated; wsa_2_3_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 14)
    - Construction Workers Taking Lunch Break on Ledge, 1984; wsa_2_3_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 15)
    - Construction Workers Taking Lunch Break on Ledge, undated; wsa_2_3_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 16)
    - South Side of East 8th Street Looking West from University Place, undated; wsa_2_3_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 3, Item 17)
  - 5th Avenue (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - MacDougal Alley or Washington Mews, May 1949; wsa_2_4_01; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - 5th Avenue between Washington Mews and Washington Square North, circa 1921; wsa_2_4_02; Baeje; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 4, Item 2)